let questions=
[

    {
        numb:1,
        question:"The class in bootstrap which is used to specify the collapsible elements is-?",
        answer:"A. .collapse",
        options:[
        "A. .collapse",
        "B. .carousel",
        "C. .pager",
        "D.  None of the above",
    ]
    },
    
    
    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a well?",
        answer:"B. .well",
        options:[
        "A. .wel",
        "B. .well",
        "C. .well-container",
        "D. .container-well",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:3,
        question:"The class used for craeting the large size wells is-?",
        answer:"A. .well-lg",
        options:[
        "A. ,well-large",
        "B. .well-big",
        "C. .well-lg",
        "D. .well-sm",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:4,
        question:"The class used for creating the small size wells is -?",
        answer:"D. .well-sm",
        options:[
        "A. .well-small",
        "B. .well-short",
        "C. .well-lg",
        "D. .well-sm",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:5,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used for creating the small size modals?",
        answer:"D. .modal-lg. ",
        options:[
        "A. .modal-large",
        "B. .modal-sm",
        "C. .modal-big",
        "D. .modal-lg",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:6,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used for creating the small size modals?",
        answer:"B. .modal-sm",
        options:[
        "A. .modal-large",
        "B. .modal-sm",
        "C. .modal-big",
        "D. .modal-lg",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to indicate the uppercased text?",
        answer:"D. .text-uppercase",
        options:[
        "A. .text-capitalize",
        "B. .text-upper",
        "C. .uppercase",
        "D. .text-uppercase",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Which of the following plugin is used to create a tooltip?",
        answer:"B. tooltip",
        options:[
        "A. popover",
        "B. tooltip",
        "C. modal",
        "D. None of the above",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:9,
        question:"Which of the following class is used to add a heading to the panel?",
        answer:"C. .panel-heading",
        options:[
        "A. .panel-head",
        "B. .panel-header",
        "C. .panel-heading",
        "D. .panel-content",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a label?",
        answer:"A. .label",
        options:[
        "A. .label",
        "B. .badge",
        "C. .flag",
        "D. .popover",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:11,
        question:"Is it true the bootstrap grid system works across multiple devices?",
        answer:"A.True ",
        options:[
        "A. True",
        "B. False",
        "C. Can't say",
        "D. May be",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:12,
        question:"What is the default layout of the  bootstrap form?",
        answer:"C. Vertical",
        options:[
        "A. Horizontal",
        "B. Inline",
        "C. Vertical",
        "D. None of the above",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:13,
        question:"Which of the following class indicates the capitalized text?",
        answer:"A. .text-capitalize ",
        options:[
        "A. .text-capitalize",
        "B. .text-uper",
        "C. .uppercase",
        "D. .text-uppercase",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:14,
        question:"The class used to right align the navigation bar buttons is-?",
        answer:"C. .navbar-right",
        options:[
        "A. .navbar-rgt",
        "B. .navbar-btn",
        "C. .navbar-right",
        "D. .navbar-default",
    ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"Which of the following class is used to create a thumbnail image?",
        answer:"D. .img-thumbnail",
        options:[
        "A. .img-circle",
        "B..img-nail ",
        "C. .img-thumb",
        "D. .img-thumbnail",
    ]
    },


];